[lawyer

](https://ailawyer.pro/)

[lawyer

](https://ailawyer.pro/)

[lawyer

](https://ailawyer.pro/)

[lawyer

](https://ailawyer.pro/)

Privacy

Privacy Policy
==============

Our promise at AI Lawyer: keeping your data safe.

Thank you for choosing our AI-Lawyer platform ("the Platform"). We understand that your privacy is important and we are committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you, how we use it, and your rights regarding the information.

#### Information we collect:

To use the Platform, we require you to provide us with your name and email address. This information is necessary to provide you with the legal advice and services you request.

#### How we use your information:

We do not share, sell, or rent your personal information to any third party for their marketing purposes. We use your name and email address only to communicate with you about your legal advice and services, and to improve our Platform. We may also use your information for analytical purposes to improve our Platform and services.

#### Your rights:

You have the right to access, correct, and delete your personal information at any time. You can do this by contacting us. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information and to lodge a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority.

#### Security:

We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We use industry-standard encryption technologies and secure servers to protect your information.

#### Changes to the policy:

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post the updated policy on our website, and your continued use of the Platform after the changes have been made will indicate your acceptance of the updated policy.

Thank you for choosing our AI-Lawyer platform ("the Platform"). We understand that your privacy is important and we are committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you, how we use it, and your rights regarding the information.

#### Information we collect:

To use the Platform, we require you to provide us with your name and email address. This information is necessary to provide you with the legal advice and services you request.

#### How we use your information:

We do not share, sell, or rent your personal information to any third party for their marketing purposes. We use your name and email address only to communicate with you about your legal advice and services, and to improve our Platform. We may also use your information for analytical purposes to improve our Platform and services.

#### Your rights:

You have the right to access, correct, and delete your personal information at any time. You can do this by contacting us. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information and to lodge a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority.

#### Security:

We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We use industry-standard encryption technologies and secure servers to protect your information.

#### Changes to the policy:

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post the updated policy on our website, and your continued use of the Platform after the changes have been made will indicate your acceptance of the updated policy.

Thank you for choosing our AI-Lawyer platform ("the Platform"). We understand that your privacy is important and we are committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you, how we use it, and your rights regarding the information.

#### Information we collect:

To use the Platform, we require you to provide us with your name and email address. This information is necessary to provide you with the legal advice and services you request.

#### How we use your information:

We do not share, sell, or rent your personal information to any third party for their marketing purposes. We use your name and email address only to communicate with you about your legal advice and services, and to improve our Platform. We may also use your information for analytical purposes to improve our Platform and services.

#### Your rights:

You have the right to access, correct, and delete your personal information at any time. You can do this by contacting us. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information and to lodge a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority.

#### Security:

We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We use industry-standard encryption technologies and secure servers to protect your information.

#### Changes to the policy:

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post the updated policy on our website, and your continued use of the Platform after the changes have been made will indicate your acceptance of the updated policy.

Thank you for choosing our AI-Lawyer platform ("the Platform"). We understand that your privacy is important and we are committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you, how we use it, and your rights regarding the information.

#### Information we collect:

To use the Platform, we require you to provide us with your name and email address. This information is necessary to provide you with the legal advice and services you request.

#### How we use your information:

We do not share, sell, or rent your personal information to any third party for their marketing purposes. We use your name and email address only to communicate with you about your legal advice and services, and to improve our Platform. We may also use your information for analytical purposes to improve our Platform and services.

#### Your rights:

You have the right to access, correct, and delete your personal information at any time. You can do this by contacting us. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information and to lodge a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority.

#### Security:

We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We use industry-standard encryption technologies and secure servers to protect your information.

#### Changes to the policy:

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post the updated policy on our website, and your continued use of the Platform after the changes have been made will indicate your acceptance of the updated policy.

##### Still have questions?

Can’t find the answer you’re looking for?Please chat to our friendly team!

[lawyer

](https://ailawyer.pro/)

##### Company

##### Product

##### Pages

© 2024 AILawtech Sp Z O O. All rights reserved.

[lawyer

](https://ailawyer.pro/)

##### Company

##### Product

##### Pages

© 2024 AILawtech Sp Z O O. All rights reserved.

[lawyer

](https://ailawyer.pro/)

##### Company

##### Product

##### Pages

© 2024 AILawtech Sp Z O O. All rights reserved.

[lawyer

](https://ailawyer.pro/)

##### Company

##### Product

##### Pages

© 2024 AILawtech Sp Z O O. All rights reserved.

© 2023 AI Lawtech Sp Z O O. All rights reserved.
